## ROSIE BRADSHAW

#### FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



### 649-993-220

hello@rosiebradshaw.com

C/del Roser 8, 08004 Barcelona

## PROFILE

I am a full-stack web developer with solid experience in Marketing and Business Operations. Fully understanding both company and customer needs has given me a clear advantatge when developing intuitive yet result-oriented user experiences.

I always look forward to a new challenge as I am constantly searching for new ways to further develop my skills.

## SKILLS

- Creative
- Analytical
- Strong Communication
- Tri-lingual English, Catalan & Spanish
- · Website builders such as Webflow
- Design tools such as Figma
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, Tailwind,
   Javascript, Typescript
- · Agile and scrum methodologies

EDUCATION

**DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP** 

850H FULL-STACK WEB

Factoría F5, Barcelona

**ANTHROPOLOGY** 

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **CO-FOUNDER AND OPERATIONS MANAGER**

Certify Education & Assessment

2020 - 2022

- Cross-departmental projects and efficiencies
- Business management and strategy
- Design, creation and maintenance of 2 company websites:
   ieltscertify.org and certifyeducation.org.
- Set-up and oversight of tools, technology and general processes

## OPERATIONS MANAGER

International House Barcelona

2018 - 2020

- Member of the Senior Management Team
- Decision making and general processes across all departments
- Special involvement in facilities, premises and technology
- Coordination and set-up of official and international language exams

# Class of 2023 MASTERS IN BIOLOGICAL

Universitat de Barcelona & Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona Class of 2013

#### **DEGREE IN BIOLOGY**

Universitat de Barcelona Class of 2012

#### LEAD MARKETING OFFICER

International House Barcelona

2014 - 2018

- Creation and execution of marketing and social media campaigns
- Communication with key stakeholders and collaborators
- Organisation and planning of national and international events
- · Educational institutions and online classroom management